Doaa Ali Mohamed Front end developer

► hanaahamdy840@gmail.com

01009389654

in linkedin.com/in/doaa-ali-96749b254

github.com/DoaaAliYounis

Profile

A Junior Front end developer, Utilized HTML, CSS, and JavaScript and modern frameworks like React.js and Angular to create visually appealing and responsive web pages that met client requirements. Worked closely with UX/UI designers to translate their designs into functional web applications. Produced websites compatible with multiple browsers.

Education

2022/10 - present Faculty of computer Science and Information System

6 October University

Professional Experience

present	Digital Egypt Pioneers Initiative (DEPI) Internship
2024/08 - present	National Telecommunication Institute (NTI) Internship
2024/08 - 2024/08	(MEAN stack) Information Technology Institute (ITI) intership
2024/07 - 2024/09	NeuronetiX company Internship

Courses

2024/03 - 2024/05	Front-End Development Meta
2023/10 - 2024/05	Front end development Diploma Mec Academy

Projects

MovieApp ☑

- A Fully controlled APIs with React.js to represent a responsive Movie App.

Restaurant Receipt App 🛭

- A unique idea for Ordering Food using React.js, APIs , JavaScript , CSS and HTML

Skills

Technologies:

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- Tailwind CSS
- Sass
- APIs
- UI/UX

Frameworks:

- Bootstrap
- React.js
- Node.js basics